RG 062:108, Town of Oxford
Connecticut State Library
Town of Oxford records
1822-1902
Connecticut State Library
Oxford (Conn.)
2 cubic feet
Administrative and school records for the town of Oxford.
RG062_108
T000308
Historical Note
The town of Oxford was incorporated in October 1798 and was taken from Derby and Southbury.
Scope and Content
Administrative and school records for the town of Oxford.
Index Terms
Subjects:
School enrollment -- Connecticut -- Oxford -- Statistics; Schools -- Connecticut -- Oxford -- History -- Sources
Places:
Oxford (Conn.) -- Records and correspondence
Restrictions on Access
These records are stored at an off-site facility and therefore may not be available on a same-day basis.
See the policy.
Container List
- Records, 1822-1902
  - Town Deposit Fund account books, 1837-1898; 2 volumes (Box Box 1)
    - 1837-1869 (Box Box 1)
    - 1870-1898 (Box Box 1)
  - Town Treasurer's account books, 1822-1899; 2 volumes
    - 1822-1870 (Volume Item 3)
    - 1870-1899 (Box Box 1)
  - Treasurer and Auditor's book, 1871 October 1-1899 September 15 (Box Box 1)
    Includes list of outstanding orders, 1854-1871, with dates when paid.
  - Town Collector's account book, 1822-1897 (Volume Item 4)
  - First School District register, 1850-1857 (Box Box 2)
  - First School District minutes, 1870-1898 (Box Box 2)
    Includes Treasurer's accounts, 1873-1879.
  - First School District Treasurer's account book, 1825-1859 (Box Box 2)
  - Second School District minutes, 1859-1895 (Box Box 2)
    Includes bounds of the Second School District, survey of 1860.
  - Third School District minutes, 1841-1890 (Box Box 2)
  - Great Hill School District register, 1901 September 9-1902 June 17 (Box Box 2)